Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Web Fiction, 1986-2003, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.; 3 electronic discs (cd-rom)
  - Playing In the Shed, Black Flag, 2002, cuid24746 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Playing With Dad 1, Phil, 2002, cuid24747 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Please, Dad!, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24748 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Pleasing My Daddy (Parts 1-6), Terry, 2002, cuid24749 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - The Plumbers, CobbleHillGuy, 2002, cuid24750 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - A Plumber's Tale, Dirt Pig, Undated; cuid24751 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Poker Buddies, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24752 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Police Bitch, Nathan Harvey, 1999, cuid24753 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - The Prime Mission (Chapters 1, 2-7, 9), Falcon30, 1998; cuid24754 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Prison Food (Parts 1- 3), Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24755 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Prison Scat (Parts 1-4), Kyle Porter, Undated; cuid24756 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Private Lessons (Parts 1-3), Rim4You, 2000, cuid24757 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - To Protect and Serve, Desert Rat, 1999, cuid24758 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Pumpin Cops, Cooper, 2000, cuid24759 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Punks, Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24760 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Put In My Place, SlaveBoy232, 2000; cuid24761 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Putrid Liquid, Micfriend, Undated; cuid24762 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Queering Sgt. Strait (Parts 1,3-5), Cooper Smith, 2000; cuid24763 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Racial Issues, Roderick Shafton, 2002, cuid24764 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Ranch Hand - From the Oracle BBS, Unknown, Undated; cuid24765 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Ranch Workout, Silicondog, Undated; cuid24766 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Raunch, Rick Wagner, 1997, cuid24767 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Raunch Night, Gayskin, Undated; cuid24768 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Raunchy Boy (Parts 1-6), Rim4You, 2001, cuid24769 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Raunchy Studs (Parts 1- 3), Rim4You, 2002, cuid24770 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Raunchy With Dad, Marc, 2001, cuid24771 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Real Chat Text - Man and 18 Year Old, l@flash.net, 1997; cuid24772 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Really Hairy Family (Parts 1,2), Story Teller, 1999; cuid24773 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - The Recycling, Twenty Bucks, 2000; cuid24774 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Redneck Fucked by Giant Black Cock, Lives to Tell Tale, R. Keith Peck, 1996; cuid24775 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - RepoMan, An668681, 1996; cuid24776 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Revenge on Private Ryan, Alex J, 2000, cuid24777 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Rick and the Bike Gang, Greg Cherry, 2000, cuid24778 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Ricky and Vito, Dirt Pig, Undated; cuid24779 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Roadside Attraction (Parts 1,2), Scatboy001, 2000; cuid24780 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Roadside Raunch, Steve Kafe, 2001; cuid24781 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Roadwork, Unknown, Undated; cuid24782 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Rocky's Summer Camp, Butc0, 1999; cuid24783 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Rocky's Summer Camp, Butch; College Crap, Pigboy; Eating Brian, Sewer Rat, Undated; cuid24784 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Rod of Might, R. Keith Peck, 1996, cuid24785 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Roofers, Scott Brenson, 1998, cuid24786 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - The Rookie, Bawdy Pen, 2003, cuid24787 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Rookie Bar Slut, Kyle_14, 2001; cuid24788 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - The Room, maipenraikhap, 2000, cuid24789 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Rough Handsome Mexican, David L. Hass, 2000; cuid24790 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Roughneck Lust, Da Cooper, 1998; cuid24791 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Roughneck Lust, Furr, 1992, cuid24792 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Roving Reporter (Parts 4,6), Bawdy Pen, 2002; cuid24793 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Sailors Do It Deeper, Slick, 1995; cuid24794 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Sam's Story, Unknown, Undated; cuid24795 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Sarge, Ralph, Undated; cuid24796 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Sarge, Butch His Dad and I (Parts 1-3), Nick, 2000; cuid24797 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Saturday Morning Raunch, Joewilson583, 2000; cuid24798 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Say Uncle, Vashon Logwood, 2000, cuid24799 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Scenes With Watersports, Slick, 1995, cuid24800 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Scent Pig (Parts 1-3), Eric_Jerry, 1999-2000; cuid24801 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Sears Stalls,1998, cuid24802 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Service Station, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24803 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Service Whore, Scedmark, 2000, cuid24804 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Sewer Rats, Mike Kliewer, 2001, cuid24805 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Sex and the Signal Guy, cgard43, 1998; cuid24806 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Sex Raunch, Bawdy Pen, 2003; cuid24807 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Sexual Assault (Parts 2,3), Phill, 1998; cuid24808 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Shane, Yard Man, David L. Hass, 2000; cuid24809 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Shane's Football Injury, Jim Allen, 2000; cuid24810 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Sharing Memories, Jason Taylor, Undated; cuid24811 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Sheriff Parker (Part 49), Sky King, 1998, cuid24812 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Sheriff Parker (Part 52), Hulcap, 2000, cuid24813 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Sheriff Parker Cock Expert (Parts 1-5), Unknown, Undated; cuid24814 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Shipping Dock Raunch, Joe Wilson, 1998, cuid24815 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Shit Fuck, Marc, 2000, cuid24816 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Shit Games, Unknown, Undated; cuid24817 (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Shit Mail (Numbers 1-6), Butch, Undated; cuid24818 (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Shit Sex 101, slick, 1997; cuid24819 (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Shit Slave, Arablover, Undated; cuid24820 (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Shitty Attraction; Mr. Ass' Story Room, Mr. Ass, Undated; cuid24821 (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Show Off, BigRedOne, 2000; cuid24822 (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Sir Let Me Drink His Piss, Anartist, 2002, cuid24823 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Skid Marks, Scatboy001, 2000; cuid24824 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - The Skinhead and His Spider, Outbacker, Undated; cuid24825 (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Slave Boy's Punishment From Master, Biker, Undated; cuid24826 (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Slave to Cock, An204073, 1995; cuid24827 (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Slave Wedding, Malestory, 1996, cuid24828 (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Sleazy Stud (Part 3), Marc, 2001, cuid24829 (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - Slugger and the Batboy, Roderick Shafton, 2000; cuid24830 (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Slut Beginnings (Part 1), Matthew Taylor, 1998; cuid24831 (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Slut Boy (1, Too & More), Billy Boy, 1999; cuid24832 (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Sneaky Intruder, Roderick Shafton, 2002; cuid24833 (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - Snotty Kid, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24834 (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - Soldier's Boy: The Moaning After (Part 2), Plow Boy OH, 1997; cuid24835 (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - Soldier's Boy: Pryed and Prejudice - Part 5, Andrew Renz, 1997; cuid24836 (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - Solo Sperm Feast in the Making, Rob, Undated; cuid24837 (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - Some Public Sex, Michael, 1999, cuid24838 (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - Southern Mechanic, PghDude, 1994, cuid24839 (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Special Gloryhole, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24840 (Box 25, Folder 121)
  - Splatter 1.1, Unknown, 1994; cuid24841 (Box 25, Folder 122)
  - The Stables, Nathan Harvey, 1999, cuid24842 (Box 25, Folder 123)
  - The Stall, Doug192, Undated; cuid24843 (Box 25, Folder 124)
  - The Stallion Rides, R. Keith Peck, 1996, cuid24844 (Box 25, Folder 125)
  - Staying with Aunt Evelyn (Parts 1-3,5,7), Roderick Shafton, 2000, cuid24845 (Box 25, Folder 126)
  - Stephen's Cock Control, Glaucon55, 2000; cuid24846 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Still a Bitch, Tom Story, 2000, cuid24847 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Story, Spanamer, 1999, cuid24848 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Story of Scott (Part 2), Strokedude29, 2000; cuid24849 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Straight (?) Brother, Balsam8, 1999; cuid24850 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Straight Buddy Ray; Straight Buddy Ray's Lil Bro Joey; and Straight Buddy Ray: Lil Joey Goes Greek; Jon Royale, 2001-2002; cuid24851 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Straight Buddy Ray's Teen-age Confidential, Jon Royale, 2002; cuid24852 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Straight Learning Curve, Aussie Slick, Undated; cuid24853 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Strange Days At The Clinic, Loopy, Undated; cuid24854 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Strictly Business, Parisboi, 1995, cuid24855 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Stroke-n-Sniff, Rim4you, 2000, cuid24856 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Stuck on the Rock, Devil Dog, 2000; Agua Para El Papi Cholo, Tommyhawk1, cuid24857 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Stud Cop on Campus (Chapter 5), PhinnyGene, 2002; cuid24858 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Subway Encounter, Dick Hunter, 2000, cuid24859 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Subway Toilet, Unknown, Undated; cuid24860 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Suck Job, Unknown, Undated; cuid24861 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - A Sudden Urge, Martel, 2000; cuid24862 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Swabby's Story, Studebaker62, 1999; cuid24863 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Swabby's Tale, Unknown, Undated; cuid24864 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Sweat, Warren Williams, 1993; cuid24865 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Sweaty Septette, David L. Hass, 2000; cuid24866 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Sweet Revenge, Bawdy Pen, 2003, cuid24867 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Swordfish (Sleepover), Darner987; (Kein Thema) Darner987; My Mouth Full, Manx952joy; Faggot- Cont., Manx952joy; His Sweaty Legs Pressed Up Against Mine, Manx952joy; The Club, Darner987, 2003; cuid24868 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The TACS Club, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24869 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Take Me to the Limit, S. Brenson, Undated; cuid24870 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Taken For A Ride, Jaime Anderson, 1999, cuid24871 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Taking A Piss, Slick, 1995, cuid24872 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Taking First Piss, Jon Himus, 2003, cuid24873 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - The Taste of Sweat, Don Azars, 1998, cuid24874 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - A Taste of Their Own Medicine, nec125, 2000; cuid24875 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Teaching Coach the Lesson (Part 1), Douglas McLeod, 1998; cuid24876 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Team Reward (Parts 1-7), Bill Drake, 2000; cuid24877 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - The Team's Morale Booster, Mike Kliewer, 2001, cuid24878 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - A Teenage Summer, Clark Smith, 2000, cuid24879 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Teens in Jocks, Warren Williams, 1993, cuid24880 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - The Telephone Conversation, Roderick Shafton, 2000; cuid24881 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Temptations Path (Parts 1,2), Joe Law, 1999; cuid24882 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Terrence Takes on His Teacher, TunsofFun, 1999; cuid24883 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Terry's Lessons (Chapter 10-11,13), Shaver Boy, 1999; cuid24884 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - That Musk Ain't Aftershave, Roderick Shafton, 2001, cuid24885 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Theater Whore (Parts 1,2), Tom Straw, 2000; cuid24886 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Theo the Janitor, Unknown; Dirt Pig at the Brown Bungalows, Dirt Pig, Undated; cuid24887 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Three Studs and a Willing Hole (Parts 2,3), Splits, 2000; cuid24888 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Through Man a Mighty River Flows, R. Keith Peck, 1997, cuid24889 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Thy Neighbors Wife and Husband, Joseph_S1, 1999; cuid24890 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Tim and Buddy, Shitbreath, Undated; cuid24891 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Timothy, Colt, 2002, cuid24892 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Titus the Cop 2, Twenty Bucks, 2002, cuid24893 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Toilet Paper, Chaoshead, 1997, cuid24894 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Toilet Sex With Dad, Rim4You, 2000, cuid24895 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Toilet Sex With Dad, Rim4You, 2000; Nasty Chat Buds (Part 2), Dude X, 2001; cuid24896 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Toilet Trash Turnaround, Lance Rush, 1999, cuid24897 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Training Continues, Isuckall, Undated; cuid24898 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Trash Man (Part 1), Unknown, Undated; cuid24899 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Trreat the Trick, Rim4You, 2001; cuid24900 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - A Trio of Truckers, cgard43, 2000; cuid24901 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Truck Rape Cop (Part 3), Copsucker_99, 2001; cuid24902 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Truck Stop, Joe Wilson, 2000, cuid24903 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Truck Stop Adventures (Parts 1-2), Joe Law, 1999, cuid24904 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Trucker Adventures (Part 2), Joe Law, 1999, cuid24905 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - The Trucker and The Biker, Steve in Hotlanta, 1994, cuid24906 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - The Trucker and the Hitchhiker Get to it, Gettooit, 1999; cuid24907 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Trucker Reunion 2001, GregBear, 2002; cuid24908 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Truckers Dream, Truckers Nightmare, Grizzy Scribe, Undated; cuid24909 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Truckers House, Anonymous, 1998, cuid24910 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Truckers Load (Parts 1,2,6,7), Mike Kliewer, 2002; cuid24911 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Trucker's Boy Toy, I.K., 2000, cuid24912 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Trucker's Gloryhole: Getting It From the Big Boys, Joey, 2000; cuid24913 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Truckhawk, GregBear, Undated; cuid24914 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Trucking With Dad and Uncle Steve, Balsam8, 2000; cuid24915 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Truckstop Latrine, Balls187, 2000; cuid24916 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Truckstop Rape (Part 1), Redragon, 1995, cuid24917 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - True Confessions of an Oklahoma Toilet Boy: A Trilogy of Turds, RimmerBoy (ScatDude); One Wednesday Afternoon, Sxuldev8, 2000; cuid24918 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - The Two Fullbacks, JamesTBell, 1999, cuid24919 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Two Men from the Barracks, Lance Kester, 1995, cuid24920 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Two New Toys, William A. Lepeak, 1998, cuid24921 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Uncle Bruno's Bedroom, Ethan Coleman, 2001, cuid24922 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Uncle Chris's Party, Joe Law, 1999, cuid24923 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Uncle Donovan (Parts 5-7, 9-11), Casey Jordan, 2000-2001; cuid24924 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Uncle Jack Takes Charge, Journey, 2000; cuid24925 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Uncle Jack Two Uncle Jake- Part 2, Bob Archman, 2000; cuid24926 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Uncle Joe, Michael D. Yoder, Undated; cuid24927 (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Uncle John - A Series, Matt Diermier, 2001, cuid24928 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Uncle Leon's Anger, Bawdy Pen, 2002, cuid24929 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Uncle Louie (Part 1), twofoldman, 2000, cuid24930 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Uncle Red's Garage, GregBear, Undated; cuid24931 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Uncles Slutboy (Parts 1,2,5,10,11,13,16,17,18), Joe Law, 1999; cuid24932 (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Under Construction, Scott Brenson, 1989, cuid24933 (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Under the Goal Posts, Eric Madsen, 2000, cuid24934 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Untitled (GDShiteater Stories) (Parts 1-4), K.R., Undated; cuid24935 (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Untitled, Kenny B, 1996; cuid24936 (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Untitled, Larry Johnson, 1991; cuid24937 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Untitled, Spanamer, 1999; cuid24938 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Untitled, Unknown, 1998; cuid24939 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - Untitled, Unknown, Undated; cuid24940 (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - UPS Fun, Unknown, Undated; cuid24941 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Used By Jock 3, Warren Greene, 2001; cuid24942 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Verbal Abuse From the Agency Jock, Kuhdupu, 2002; cuid24943 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Video (Part 2), Lilglex666, Undated; cuid24944 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Video Booth (Part 1), LilAlex666, Undated; cuid24945 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Video Booth Head (Chapters 1,2), Noone and PupDoesIt, 1996; cuid24946 (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - A Vignette, Dale1, 2000; cuid24947 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - The Vikes With the Bike, David L. Hass, 2000; cuid24948 (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - Vivid Imagination, Anthony, 2000, cuid24949 (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - Wanting More Raunch (Parts 1-3), Steve Kafe, 2001-2002; cuid24950 (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - The Warehouse 2, Fleetwood, 2002, cuid24951 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Watching the Miners (Parts 1- 8), Peter Nixon, 2001-2002; cuid24952 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - The Waterboy, Boysub3; Jock Doc, David White; Locker Room, Jerry Gaither, Undated; cuid24953 (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - We Three As Told By Jon Hold, Jon Hold, 2000, cuid24954 (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - Wedding Ball Blueboys, Jon Royale, 2001, cuid24955 (Box 26, Folder 110)
  - The Wedding Gift, Maipenraikhap, 1999-2000; cuid24956 (Box 26, Folder 111)
  - Weekend at the Lake, proflew, Undated; cuid24957 (Box 26, Folder 112)
  - Weekend Liberty in San Diego, MaheimEins, 2000, cuid24958 (Box 26, Folder 113)
  - Welcome to the Joint, Cocksucker, Ivan the Gypsy, Undated; cuid24959 (Box 26, Folder 114)
  - Wet and Messy (Volumes 1-4), Stephen Holden, Undated; cuid24960 (Box 26, Folder 115)
  - Wet Boy, Hal Courtenay, 1999; cuid24961 (Box 26, Folder 116)
  - A Wet Evening, Stephen Brown, 1997, cuid24962 (Box 26, Folder 117)
  - What I Saw (Part 1), Bobysboi, 2000, cuid24963 (Box 26, Folder 118)
  - Where ya headed, Sarge?; Steve Giammarco, 1996; cuid24964 (Box 26, Folder 119)
  - While the Cat's Away (Part 3), Policefan36, 2001; cuid24965 (Box 26, Folder 120)
  - Whoring With Dad (Part 1), Gloryhole_junkie, Undated; cuid24966 (Box 26, Folder 121)
  - Wilson's Hollow (Parts 4, 6), Bob Archman, 2002; cuid24967 (Box 26, Folder 122)
  - The Workman, Da Copper, 1998; cuid24968 (Box 26, Folder 123)
  - YMCA (Part 2), Trainman, Undated; cuid24969 (Box 26, Folder 124)
  - You Know You Like It, Stevey, Undated; cuid24970 (Box 26, Folder 125)
  - CD-R discs titled "Nifty" with saved story files (3 discs), 2004-2005; cuid25278 (Box 26, Folder 126)
- Series IX. Films, 1981-2007, undated; 6 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons.; 173 videocassettes (vhs); 120 videodiscs (dvd)
  Organized into two subseries:
  Subseries IX.A. Videocassettes (VHS), 1981-2004, undated
  Subseries IX.B. Videodiscs (DVD), 1995-2007, undated
  This series contains gay pornographic films recorded on VHS and DVD.
  - Subseries IX.A. Videocassettes (VHS), 1981-2004, undated; 4 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons.; 173 videocassettes (vhs)
    The VHS tapes are listed alphabetically by title, followed by production company name.
    This subseries consists of gay pornographic films in VHS format, covering a variety of sexual interests and themes.
    - Amazon Adventures, Kristen Bjorn, Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 1996; cuid24971 (Box 27)
    - Animals, Paul Morris, California, Palm Drive Video, 2000; cuid24972 (Box 27)
    - Ass Lick Alley, All Worlds Video, 1998; cuid24973 (Box 27)
    - Barracks Glory Hole #6, 1996; cuid24974 (Box 27)
    - Before & After, California, SX Video, Undated; cuid24975 (Box 27)
    - BHV - 9 Hog's Banquet, Undated; cuid24976 (Box 27)
    - BHV 7 - Very Yellow with Stains of Brown, Undated; cuid24977 (Box 27)
    - Basic Training S.F + Horseman 2000, Undated; cuid24978 (Box 27)
    - The Best of Frank Vickers, Christoper Rage, 1991; cuid24979 (Box 27)
    - Bic: Cop Interludes, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid24980 (Box 27)
    - Bic: Cops & Throbbers, California, Palm Drive Video, 1995; cuid24981 (Box 27)
    - Bic: Sex Ptrol, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid24982 (Box 27)
    - Big Bruno, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid24983 (Box 27)
    - Big Guns, California, Laguna Pacific Ltd Video, 1984; cuid24984 (Box 27)
    - Billy Herrington's Body Shop, California, All Worlds Video, 1997; cuid24985 (Box 27)
    - Blue Collar White Socks, T&T Productions, 1997; cuid24986 (Box 27)
    - Blue Collar: White Heat, California, Vivid Video, Undated; cuid24987 (Box 27)
    - Bulge, Undated; cuid24988 (Box 27)
    - Bones for Cumpuppy, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2000; cuid24989 (Box 27)
    - Born to Serve, Undated; cuid24990 (Box 27)
    - Bottoms, Jack Stone, Live Video, Undated; cuid24991 (Box 27)
    - Boys in the Attic, Undated; cuid24992 (Box 27)
    - Breakin 'em In, California, Marco Studio, 1997; cuid24993 (Box 27)
    - Breed Me, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 1999; cuid24994 (Box 27)
    - The Brick Wall, T&T Productions, Undated; cuid24995 (Box 27)
    - The Brig, HIS Video, 1986; cuid24996 (Box 27)
    - Bruce #1, Undated; cuid24997 (Box 27)
    - Brute, Undated; cuid24998 (Box 27)
    - BuckleRoos Part 1, California, Colt Studio, 2004; cuid24999 (Box 27)
    - Bullet Productions Video Pac 2, California, 1982; cuid25000 (Box 27)
    - Bullet Productions Video Pac 4, Undated; cuid25001 (Box 27)
    - Bullet Productions Video Pac 6, Undated; cuid25002 (Box 27)
    - Buster: The Best Years, Jocks Presents, Undated; cuid25003 (Box 27)
    - Butt Munch, California, All World's Video, 1998; cuid25004 (Box 27)
    - Butt Munch #2 'Back to the Crack', California, All Worlds Video, 1999; cuid25005 (Box 27)
    - Caged, Jack Stone, Undated; cuid25006 (Box 27)
    - The Caracas Adventure, Kristen Bjorn, Florida, Kristen Bjorn Productions, 1995; cuid25007 (Box 27)
    - Circus of Sex, Undated; cuid25008 (Box 27)
    - The Complexxx, California, All World's Video, 1998; cuid25009 (Box 27)
    - Cowboy Bunkhouse Muscle Cigar Jo, California, Palm Drive Video, Undated; cuid25010 (Box 27)
    - Cum in My Ass 1, SX Video, Undated; cuid25011 (Box 27)
    - Custom Tape #3: BR1, Undated; cuid25012 (Box 27)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 60 minutes
      Content warning: Strong sexual content
    - Custom #5: Easy Assplay, Undated; cuid25013 (Box 27)
    - Custom Tape #6 - BR2, Undated; cuid25014 (Box 27)
    - Daddy's Big Dump! + Hoursemen part 1, Undated; cuid25015 (Box 28)
    - Daddy's Piss Party, Undated; cuid25016 (Box 28)
    - Damon Blows America - vol. 2, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2002; cuid25017 (Box 28)
    - Damon Blows America - vol. 4, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2003; cuid25018 (Box 28)
    - Damon Blows America, vol.5, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2003; cuid25019 (Box 28)
    - Descent, Hot House Entertainment, 1999; cuid25020 (Box 28)
    - Dickey Lickey, Christoper Rage, 1990; cuid25021 (Box 28)
    - Dickie Lickie, Undated; cuid25022 (Box 28)
    - Doing It, MT Productions, Undated; cuid25023 (Box 28)
    - Down Home, California, Falcon, Undated; cuid25024 (Box 28)
    - Driven: No Turning Back, California, Falcon, Undated; cuid25025 (Box 28)
    - Drunk on Cum - Part 1, Paul Morris, California, Treasure Island Media, 2003; cuid25026 (Box 28)
    - Drunk on Cum - Part 2, Treasure Island Media, 2003; cuid25027 (Box 28)
    - Easy Entry - various titles, Buckshot Productions, Undated; cuid25028 (Box 28)
    - El Paso: Wrecking Corp, Joe Gage, HIS Video, 1990; cuid25029 (Box 28)
    - Fallen Angel, California, Titan Media, 1997; cuid25030 (Box 28)
    - Fallen Angel III, California, Titan Media, 1999; cuid25031 (Box 28)
    - The Final Link, California, All Worlds Video, 1999; cuid25032 (Box 28)
    - First Party Tape, Christoper Rage, 1990; cuid25033 (Box 28)
    - Full Load, California, Laguna Pacific Ltd Video, 1984; cuid25034 (Box 28)
    - Glory Hole Pigs, Undated; cuid25035 (Box 28)
    - Glory Hole Studs Video #1 - Glory Hole Cum Dump, Glory Hole Studs, 2002; cuid25036 (Box 28)
    - Glory Hole Studs Video #1 - Pump It, Dump It, Laterz, Glory Hole Studs, 2001; cuid25037 (Box 28)
    - Glory Hole Studs Video #2 - Show Hard for the Head, Glory Hole Studs, 2001; cuid25038 (Box 28)
    - Gloryhole: Tom's Foreskin Obsession, California, Palm Drive Video, 1988; cuid25039 (Box 28)
    - Gluteus MaXXXimus, Undated; cuid25040 (Box 28)
    - Go For The Flow, Undated; cuid25041 (Box 28)
    - Gold Bullet vol.2, California, Bullet Productions, 1988; cuid25042 (Box 28)
    - Hairy 9-Inch Sweathog Jerkoff, California, Palm Drive Video, 1987; cuid25043 (Box 28)
    - Hog Wild, Jack Stone, Undated; cuid25044 (Box 28)
    - Home Grown, California, Mustang Home Video, Undated; cuid25045 (Box 28)